<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<document-metadata version="1.0" xmlns="http://breeze.macromedia.com/">
	<document-info>
		<title></title>
		<summary></summary>
		<author/>
		<keywords/>
		<view-link href="/index.htm?slide={{position}}" href-html5="/index.htm?slide={{position}}" href-swf="/viewer.swf?slide={{position}}"/>
	</document-info>
	<section type="slide" position="1" xmlns="">
		<title></title>
		<content>In the name of God Research Methodology Subject 1: Fundamentals of Research Elham Akhondzadeh Noughabi Assistant Professor, Department of Information Technology Engineering, Faculty of Industrial and Systems Engineering, Tarbiat Modares University 2020 In the name of God Research Methodology Subject 1: Fundamentals of Research Elham Akhondzadeh Noughabi Assistant Professor, Department of Information Technology Engineering, Faculty of Industrial and Systems Engineering, Tarbiat Modares University 2020 </content>
		<related-content></related-content>
	</section>
	<section type="slide" position="2" xmlns="">
		<title>The Nature of Research - Definition</title>
		<content>The Nature of Research - Definition Definition: ‘Something that people undertake in order to find things out in a systematic way, thereby increasing their knowledge’  Saunders et al. (2009)  Characteristics:  Data are collected systematically  Data are interpreted systematically There is a clear purpose to find things out 	  Elham Akhondzadeh, 2020 The Nature of Research - Definition Definition: ‘Something that people undertake in order to find things out in a systematic way, thereby increasing their knowledge’  Saunders et al. (2009)  Characteristics:  Data are collected systematically  Data are interpreted systematically There is a clear purpose to find things out 	  Elham Akhondzadeh, 2020 </content>
		<related-content></related-content>
	</section>
	<section type="slide" position="3" xmlns="">
		<title>What is Research? </title>
		<content>What is Research?  Research is a combination of both experience &amp;amp; reasoning and must be regarded as the most successful approach to the discovery of truth (particularly in natural sciences) A voyage of discovery; A journey; An attitude; An experience; A method of critical thinking; A careful critical enquiry  in seeking facts for principles An art of scientific investigation, Scientific and systematic search for pertinent information on a specific topic A systematized effort to gain new knowledge; A movement from the known to the unknown     Elham Akhondzadeh, 2020 What is Research?  Research is a combination of both experience &amp;amp; reasoning and must be regarded as the most successful approach to the discovery of truth (particularly in natural sciences) A voyage of discovery; A journey; An attitude; An experience; A method of critical thinking; A careful critical enquiry  in seeking facts for principles An art of scientific investigation, Scientific and systematic search for pertinent information on a specific topic A systematized effort to gain new knowledge; A movement from the known to the unknown     Elham Akhondzadeh, 2020 </content>
		<related-content></related-content>
	</section>
	<section type="slide" position="4" xmlns="">
		<title>Research – Definition </title>
		<content>Business &amp;amp; Management Research A process of determining, acquiring,&amp;#x0A;analyzing, synthesizing, and disseminating&amp;#x0A;relevant business data, information, and&amp;#x0A;insights to decision makers in ways that&amp;#x0A;mobilize the organization to take &amp;#x0A;appropriate business actions that, &amp;#x0A;in turn, maximize business performance Research – Definition  Elham Akhondzadeh, 2020  Business &amp;amp; Management Research A process of determining, acquiring,&amp;#x0A;analyzing, synthesizing, and disseminating&amp;#x0A;relevant business data, information, and&amp;#x0A;insights to decision makers in ways that&amp;#x0A;mobilize the organization to take &amp;#x0A;appropriate business actions that, &amp;#x0A;in turn, maximize business performance Research – Definition  Elham Akhondzadeh, 2020  </content>
		<related-content>&lt;TextFlow xmlns = "http://ns.adobe.com/textLayout/2008" fontFamily = "Verdana" fontSize = "9"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span &gt;Business research is a systematic inquiry that provides information to guide business decisions. The definition, as expanded by that used by the American Marketing Association, is provided in the slide. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span &gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span &gt;Ask students to offer examples of types of decision-making situations that could be addressed using business research.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span &gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/TextFlow&gt;</related-content>
	</section>
	<section type="slide" position="5" xmlns="">
		<title>Characteristics of Good Research</title>
		<content>1-  Characteristics of Good Research  Clearly defined purposeDetailed research processThoroughly planned designHigh ethical standardsLimitations addressedAdequate analysisUnambiguous presentationValidated results Elham Akhondzadeh, 2020 1-  Characteristics of Good Research  Clearly defined purposeDetailed research processThoroughly planned designHigh ethical standardsLimitations addressedAdequate analysisUnambiguous presentationValidated results Elham Akhondzadeh, 2020 </content>
		<related-content>&lt;TextFlow xmlns = "http://ns.adobe.com/textLayout/2008" fontFamily = "Verdana" fontSize = "9"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span &gt;Exhibit 1-8 presents the characteristics of good business research and also explains what managers should look for in research done by others. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span &gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span &gt;You might wish to discuss the concepts here, before you discuss who actually conducts research…or you might want to discuss who conducts research first, followed by this slide to summarize.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span &gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/TextFlow&gt;</related-content>
	</section>
	<section type="slide" position="6" xmlns="">
		<title>Characteristics of Good Research</title>
		<content>Characteristics of Good Research  SYSTEMATIC - but does not rule out creative thinking LOGICAL - logical reasoning &amp;amp; logical process  EMPIRICAL- based on, concerned with, or verifiable by observation or experience rather than theory or pure logic &amp;amp; provides a basis for external validity to results (validation) Characteristics:  Data are collected systematically  Data are interpreted systematically There is a clear purpose to find things out  Elham Akhondzadeh, 2020 Characteristics of Good Research  SYSTEMATIC - but does not rule out creative thinking LOGICAL - logical reasoning &amp;amp; logical process  EMPIRICAL- based on, concerned with, or verifiable by observation or experience rather than theory or pure logic &amp;amp; provides a basis for external validity to results (validation) Characteristics:  Data are collected systematically  Data are interpreted systematically There is a clear purpose to find things out  Elham Akhondzadeh, 2020 </content>
		<related-content>&lt;TextFlow xmlns = "http://ns.adobe.com/textLayout/2008" fontFamily = "Verdana" fontSize = "9"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span &gt;based on, concerned with, or verifiable by observation or experience rather than theory or pure logic.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span &gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/TextFlow&gt;</related-content>
	</section>
	<section type="slide" position="7" xmlns="">
		<title>Thinking Like a Good Researcher</title>
		<content>2-  Curiosity is necessary to be a good researcher  Critical thinking   Creativity  Passion Thinking Like a Good Researcher 2-  Curiosity is necessary to be a good researcher  Critical thinking   Creativity  Passion Thinking Like a Good Researcher </content>
		<related-content>&lt;TextFlow xmlns = "http://ns.adobe.com/textLayout/2008" fontFamily = "Verdana" fontSize = "9"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span &gt;This ad from Synovate reinforces the notion that researchers must be curious. Students can see the Synovate website at www.synovate.com.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span &gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/TextFlow&gt;</related-content>
	</section>
	<section type="slide" position="8" xmlns="">
		<title>What is Research Methodology</title>
		<content>What is Research Methodology 'Research methodology' refers to the study of research methods. It does not admit of a plural. The theory of how research should be undertaken  Saunders et al. (2009)  	  A science of studying how research is done scientifically A way to systematically solve the research problem by logically adopting various steps Aims to describe and analyze methods and throw light on their limitations an benefits Researchers should know the relevant method and which are not, know the logic behind the methods we use in the context of our research study and explain why we are using a particular method and why we are not using others  Elham Akhondzadeh, 2020 What is Research Methodology 'Research methodology' refers to the study of research methods. It does not admit of a plural. The theory of how research should be undertaken  Saunders et al. (2009)  	  A science of studying how research is done scientifically A way to systematically solve the research problem by logically adopting various steps Aims to describe and analyze methods and throw light on their limitations an benefits Researchers should know the relevant method and which are not, know the logic behind the methods we use in the context of our research study and explain why we are using a particular method and why we are not using others  Elham Akhondzadeh, 2020 </content>
		<related-content></related-content>
	</section>
	<section type="slide" position="9" xmlns="">
		<title>  Terminology: Research Methodology vs. Research Method vs. Research Technique </title>
		<content>&amp;#x0A; Terminology: Research Methodology vs. Research Method vs. Research Technique   'Research technique/ Instrument‘: refers to a specific means, approach, or tool-and-its-use, whereby data is gathered and analyzed, and inferences are drawn. 'Research method' refers to the manner in which a particular research project is undertaken. The techniques and procedures used to obtain and analyze data. 'Research methodology' refers to the study of research methods. It does not admit of a plural. The theory of how research should be undertaken   Elham Akhondzadeh, 2020 &amp;#x0A; Terminology: Research Methodology vs. Research Method vs. Research Technique   'Research technique/ Instrument‘: refers to a specific means, approach, or tool-and-its-use, whereby data is gathered and analyzed, and inferences are drawn. 'Research method' refers to the manner in which a particular research project is undertaken. The techniques and procedures used to obtain and analyze data. 'Research methodology' refers to the study of research methods. It does not admit of a plural. The theory of how research should be undertaken   Elham Akhondzadeh, 2020 </content>
		<related-content></related-content>
	</section>
	<section type="slide" position="10" xmlns="">
		<title>Aims of Research</title>
		<content>Aims of Research  Discover new information or relationships; to expand and to verify existing knowledge  Develop and provide new knowledge; discovery of general principles  Theory building  Investigation of hypothetical propositions about the presumed relations among natural phenomena  To solve problems and for decision making purposes (business &amp;amp; management research) Increase our power to understand &amp;amp; explain, predict, describe &amp;amp; change   Elham Akhondzadeh, 2020 Aims of Research  Discover new information or relationships; to expand and to verify existing knowledge  Develop and provide new knowledge; discovery of general principles  Theory building  Investigation of hypothetical propositions about the presumed relations among natural phenomena  To solve problems and for decision making purposes (business &amp;amp; management research) Increase our power to understand &amp;amp; explain, predict, describe &amp;amp; change   Elham Akhondzadeh, 2020 </content>
		<related-content></related-content>
	</section>
	<section type="slide" position="11" xmlns="">
		<title>Goals of Research</title>
		<content>Goals of Research One of the most basic decisions a researcher must take is about what the goal of his or her research is going to be.  Research in science generally focuses on one or more of the following goals: Description, Prediction, Explanatory (understand) and/or Change (evaluation).  Elham Akhondzadeh, 2020 Goals of Research One of the most basic decisions a researcher must take is about what the goal of his or her research is going to be.  Research in science generally focuses on one or more of the following goals: Description, Prediction, Explanatory (understand) and/or Change (evaluation).  Elham Akhondzadeh, 2020 </content>
		<related-content></related-content>
	</section>
	<section type="slide" position="12" xmlns="">
		<title>Descriptive Research </title>
		<content>Descriptive Research   Descriptive Research has as its goal description, or the attempt to discover facts or describe reality. It is a picture or account of what exists, usually summarized in numbers, percentages, or some other statistics.  Elham Akhondzadeh, 2020 Descriptive Research   Descriptive Research has as its goal description, or the attempt to discover facts or describe reality. It is a picture or account of what exists, usually summarized in numbers, percentages, or some other statistics.  Elham Akhondzadeh, 2020 </content>
		<related-content></related-content>
	</section>
	<section type="slide" position="13" xmlns="">
		<title>Predictive Research</title>
		<content>Predictive Research Focuses on prediction, or making projection about what may occur in the future or in other settings.  It uses present knowledge to predict what would expect to find at another time or place. Impact assessments, conducted by scientists, are an attempt to predict the impacts on the environment.  Elham Akhondzadeh, 2020 Predictive Research Focuses on prediction, or making projection about what may occur in the future or in other settings.  It uses present knowledge to predict what would expect to find at another time or place. Impact assessments, conducted by scientists, are an attempt to predict the impacts on the environment.  Elham Akhondzadeh, 2020 </content>
		<related-content></related-content>
	</section>
	<section type="slide" position="14" xmlns="">
		<title>Explanatory Research (Understand) </title>
		<content>Explanatory Research (Understand)  Involves explanation, understanding or determining why or how something occurred.  It goes beyond description by trying to find causes of some phenomenon, and it strives to develop and verify theories as explanatory systems.  Elham Akhondzadeh, 2020 Explanatory Research (Understand)  Involves explanation, understanding or determining why or how something occurred.  It goes beyond description by trying to find causes of some phenomenon, and it strives to develop and verify theories as explanatory systems.  Elham Akhondzadeh, 2020 </content>
		<related-content></related-content>
	</section>
	<section type="slide" position="15" xmlns="">
		<title>Explanatory vs. Predictive Research </title>
		<content>Explanatory vs. Predictive Research   The goal of explanation may appear to be quite similar to that of prediction, but there is a difference: One can make predictions without an accompanying explanation.  Actuaries at insurance companies do the all the time by calculating risks and premium levels for insurance policies. From data or past automobile accidents, for example, they predict that young males will- for whatever reasons- have more accidents than older people and females, and their insurance rates reflect this fact.  Elham Akhondzadeh, 2020 Explanatory vs. Predictive Research   The goal of explanation may appear to be quite similar to that of prediction, but there is a difference: One can make predictions without an accompanying explanation.  Actuaries at insurance companies do the all the time by calculating risks and premium levels for insurance policies. From data or past automobile accidents, for example, they predict that young males will- for whatever reasons- have more accidents than older people and females, and their insurance rates reflect this fact.  Elham Akhondzadeh, 2020 </content>
		<related-content></related-content>
	</section>
	<section type="slide" position="16" xmlns="">
		<title>Evaluation Research (Change)</title>
		<content>Evaluation Research (Change) Focuses on evaluation, or the use of scientific research methods to plan changes and assess the researcher interventions and programs. Evaluation research is, in a sense, an extension of the three previous goals because it typically uses some combination of description, prediction, and explanation in order to achieve the goal of evaluation and change in reality. 	  Elham Akhondzadeh, 2020 Evaluation Research (Change) Focuses on evaluation, or the use of scientific research methods to plan changes and assess the researcher interventions and programs. Evaluation research is, in a sense, an extension of the three previous goals because it typically uses some combination of description, prediction, and explanation in order to achieve the goal of evaluation and change in reality. 	  Elham Akhondzadeh, 2020 </content>
		<related-content></related-content>
	</section>
	<section type="slide" position="17" xmlns="">
		<title>Basic and applied research</title>
		<content>Basic and applied research Basic and Applied Research in Business &amp;amp; Management Research  Sources: authors’ experience; Easterby-Smith et al. (2008); Hedrick et al. (1993)  Figure 1.1  Basic and applied research Elham Akhondzadeh, 2020  Basic and applied research Basic and Applied Research in Business &amp;amp; Management Research  Sources: authors’ experience; Easterby-Smith et al. (2008); Hedrick et al. (1993)  Figure 1.1  Basic and applied research Elham Akhondzadeh, 2020  </content>
		<related-content></related-content>
	</section>
	<section type="slide" position="18" xmlns="">
		<title>For Fun</title>
		<content>For Fun   Elham Akhondzadeh, 2020 For Fun   Elham Akhondzadeh, 2020 </content>
		<related-content></related-content>
	</section>
	<section type="slide" position="19" xmlns="">
		<title>VW Model </title>
		<content>VW Model    Elham Akhondzadeh, 2020 Developed by Prof. Amir Albadvi VW Model    Elham Akhondzadeh, 2020 Developed by Prof. Amir Albadvi </content>
		<related-content></related-content>
	</section>
	<section type="slide" position="20" xmlns="">
		<title>Qualification of Your Research</title>
		<content>Qualification of Your Research  Underlying all discussions about research is the question of what quality of research means. This in turn depends on the objectives that are ascribed to it.   Rigor &amp;amp; Relevance If the primary purpose of research is to increase the pool of abstract knowledge, then the criteria of quality are inherently internal, and rigor is critical.  If, on the other hand, the primary purpose of research is to contribute to the practice of organizations (instrumentalist approach), then the criteria are external, and relevance is much more important, and rigor of process is a constraint.  Elham Akhondzadeh, 2020 Qualification of Your Research  Underlying all discussions about research is the question of what quality of research means. This in turn depends on the objectives that are ascribed to it.   Rigor &amp;amp; Relevance If the primary purpose of research is to increase the pool of abstract knowledge, then the criteria of quality are inherently internal, and rigor is critical.  If, on the other hand, the primary purpose of research is to contribute to the practice of organizations (instrumentalist approach), then the criteria are external, and relevance is much more important, and rigor of process is a constraint.  Elham Akhondzadeh, 2020 </content>
		<related-content></related-content>
	</section>
	<section type="slide" position="21" xmlns="">
		<title>The bottom line</title>
		<content>The bottom line There is no one best way for undertaking all research Saunders et al. (2009)    This means you will be able to make an informed choice about the approaches, strategies and methods that are most suitable to your own research project, be able to justify this choice and develop your own research method for your research.    Elham Akhondzadeh, 2020 The bottom line There is no one best way for undertaking all research Saunders et al. (2009)    This means you will be able to make an informed choice about the approaches, strategies and methods that are most suitable to your own research project, be able to justify this choice and develop your own research method for your research.    Elham Akhondzadeh, 2020 </content>
		<related-content></related-content>
	</section>
	<section type="slide" position="22" xmlns="">
		<title>What are some typical examples of research areas in IT?</title>
		<content>What are some typical examples of&amp;#x0A;research areas in IT? Big Data &amp;amp; Data Science Artificial Intelligence  Complex Network &amp;amp; Social Network Analysis Security (Computer security, cybersecurity or IT security) Networks  Business Information Technology  IT Management Digitization &amp;amp; Digital Transformation  Some other fields like Cloud Computing, IOT (Internet of Things) &amp;amp;  Blockchain Applications: CRM, Marketing and E-commerce,  IT &amp;amp; Healthcare Engineering, Finance and etc.  Statistics, Mathematical &amp;amp; Data Science techniques  Elham Akhondzadeh, 2020 What are some typical examples of&amp;#x0A;research areas in IT? Big Data &amp;amp; Data Science Artificial Intelligence  Complex Network &amp;amp; Social Network Analysis Security (Computer security, cybersecurity or IT security) Networks  Business Information Technology  IT Management Digitization &amp;amp; Digital Transformation  Some other fields like Cloud Computing, IOT (Internet of Things) &amp;amp;  Blockchain Applications: CRM, Marketing and E-commerce,  IT &amp;amp; Healthcare Engineering, Finance and etc.  Statistics, Mathematical &amp;amp; Data Science techniques  Elham Akhondzadeh, 2020 </content>
		<related-content></related-content>
	</section>
	<section type="slide" position="23" xmlns="">
		<title>Research purposes in IT</title>
		<content>Research purposes in IT Improvement of IT applications: IT implementation issues at the organizational level: Research on inter-organizational IT implementation &amp;amp; Factors critical to the success and/or failure of implementation projects and management of IT  Understanding of IT related issues/phenomena: IT impact on organization culture, factors that affect adaptability of IT by people, IT &amp;amp; change management  IT systems development: design and development of IT systems for more effective applications and to develop new applications  Elham Akhondzadeh, 2020 Research purposes in IT Improvement of IT applications: IT implementation issues at the organizational level: Research on inter-organizational IT implementation &amp;amp; Factors critical to the success and/or failure of implementation projects and management of IT  Understanding of IT related issues/phenomena: IT impact on organization culture, factors that affect adaptability of IT by people, IT &amp;amp; change management  IT systems development: design and development of IT systems for more effective applications and to develop new applications  Elham Akhondzadeh, 2020 </content>
		<related-content></related-content>
	</section>
	<section type="slide" position="24" xmlns="">
		<title>Why Data Science?</title>
		<content>Why Data Science? Nowadays, data is everywhere, collectable, storable, and can potentially be usable …   Business Question: How can we use this data? (what does this data actually convey or imply?) Commercial Viewpoint: Competitive pressure is strong, maintaining edge over competitors Scientific Viewpoint: Traditional techniques infeasible for raw data (e.g. fusion, similarities, cold-cases, etc.)   How can companies analyze and use this data to gain benefit and build competitive advantage?   The big challenge is &amp;quot;how to turn data into useful knowledge“ Data is the New Oil Elham Akhondzadeh, 2020 Why Data Science? Nowadays, data is everywhere, collectable, storable, and can potentially be usable …   Business Question: How can we use this data? (what does this data actually convey or imply?) Commercial Viewpoint: Competitive pressure is strong, maintaining edge over competitors Scientific Viewpoint: Traditional techniques infeasible for raw data (e.g. fusion, similarities, cold-cases, etc.)   How can companies analyze and use this data to gain benefit and build competitive advantage?   The big challenge is &amp;quot;how to turn data into useful knowledge“ Data is the New Oil Elham Akhondzadeh, 2020 </content>
		<related-content>&lt;TextFlow xmlns = "http://ns.adobe.com/textLayout/2008" fontFamily = "Verdana" fontSize = "9"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span &gt;Now, it is the age of data and information. We have lots of data everywhere; climate data, ATM data, satellite data, biological data and etc. Many organizations have collected and stored a wealth huge amount of data about their current customers, potential customers, their transactions and etc. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span &gt;However, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span &gt;great weakness is the lack of knowledge; they don’t have a clue as to what any of that data actually means and how it can build competitive advantage for companies. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span &gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span &gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span &gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span &gt;Commercial Viewpoint: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span &gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span &gt;Computers have become cheaper and more powerful&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span &gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span &gt;Competitive Pressure is Strong: Provide better, customized services for an &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span  fontStyle="italic"&gt;edge &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span &gt;(e.g. in Customer Relationship Management)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span &gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span &gt;Scientific Viewpoint:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span &gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span &gt;Traditional techniques infeasible for raw data&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span &gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span &gt;Need techniques that can automatically&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span &gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span &gt;analyze the data and form new hypotheses for further evaluation by scientists&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span &gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span &gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span &gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span &gt;So, the main question here is: How can companies use and analyze this data to improve benefit and build competitive advantage? (The necessity and need for techniques that can automatically analyze the data and extract valuable and hidden knowledge)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span &gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/TextFlow&gt;</related-content>
	</section>
	<section type="slide" position="25" xmlns="">
		<title>What is the Solution?</title>
		<content>What is the Solution? Data science is the solution Data science is an interdisciplinary field of scientific methods, processes, algorithms and systems to extract knowledge or insights from large amounts of data in various forms, either structured or unstructured  Large Amount of Complex Data  Valuable Knowledge Data Science Dhar (2013) and Leek (2013) Data characteristics: Dynamic, Correlated, Non-stationary,  High variance,  Skewed Elham Akhondzadeh, 2020 What is the Solution? Data science is the solution Data science is an interdisciplinary field of scientific methods, processes, algorithms and systems to extract knowledge or insights from large amounts of data in various forms, either structured or unstructured  Large Amount of Complex Data  Valuable Knowledge Data Science Dhar (2013) and Leek (2013) Data characteristics: Dynamic, Correlated, Non-stationary,  High variance,  Skewed Elham Akhondzadeh, 2020 </content>
		<related-content>&lt;TextFlow xmlns = "http://ns.adobe.com/textLayout/2008" fontFamily = "Verdana" fontSize = "9"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span &gt;Data science is the solution and answers to this question.     &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span &gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span &gt;Data science tools/techniques could help these organizations to discover valuable information and hidden knowledge of data&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span &gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/TextFlow&gt;</related-content>
	</section>
	<section type="slide" position="26" xmlns="">
		<title>Data Science – A Definition</title>
		<content>Data Science – A Definition  Data Science is an interdisciplinary, problem-solving oriented subject which provides us with scientific techniques/tools to apply to practical problems. Data Science is the science which uses computer science, statistics and machine learning, visualization and human-computer interactions to collect, clean, integrate, analyze, visualize, interact with data to create data products (the goal of Data Science).   Elham Akhondzadeh, 2020 Data Science – A Definition  Data Science is an interdisciplinary, problem-solving oriented subject which provides us with scientific techniques/tools to apply to practical problems. Data Science is the science which uses computer science, statistics and machine learning, visualization and human-computer interactions to collect, clean, integrate, analyze, visualize, interact with data to create data products (the goal of Data Science).   Elham Akhondzadeh, 2020 </content>
		<related-content></related-content>
	</section>
	<section type="slide" position="27" xmlns="">
		<title>Data Science - Applications</title>
		<content>Data Science - Applications Marketing &amp;amp; Customer Relationship Management Retailing Telecommunication  Quality Control Management Maintenance  Fraud Detection Web Mining Text Mining Sports Healthcare Etc.    Elham Akhondzadeh, 2020 Data Science - Applications Marketing &amp;amp; Customer Relationship Management Retailing Telecommunication  Quality Control Management Maintenance  Fraud Detection Web Mining Text Mining Sports Healthcare Etc.    Elham Akhondzadeh, 2020 </content>
		<related-content>&lt;TextFlow xmlns = "http://ns.adobe.com/textLayout/2008" fontFamily = "Verdana" fontSize = "9"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span &gt;The different perspectives of a clinical laboratory setting.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span &gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span &gt;This figure shows the different perspectives of a clinical laboratory setting. The clinical section managers (i.e., general pathology, clinical biochemistry, microbiology, hematology, and cytopathology) can use the framework to plan for clinical lab workload and demand forecasting.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span &gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/TextFlow&gt;</related-content>
	</section>
	<section type="slide" position="28" xmlns="">
		<title>Data Science - Methodology</title>
		<content>Data Science - Methodology CRoss Industry Standard Process for Data Mining (CRISP-DM): still the top methodology for analytics, data mining, or data science projects   Shearer (2000), Harper et al. (2006) and Rollins (2015) Six major phases Elham Akhondzadeh, 2020 Data Science - Methodology CRoss Industry Standard Process for Data Mining (CRISP-DM): still the top methodology for analytics, data mining, or data science projects   Shearer (2000), Harper et al. (2006) and Rollins (2015) Six major phases Elham Akhondzadeh, 2020 </content>
		<related-content>&lt;TextFlow xmlns = "http://ns.adobe.com/textLayout/2008" fontFamily = "Verdana" fontSize = "9"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span &gt;CRISP-DM breaks the process of data analytics/mining into six major phases.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span &gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span &gt;The sequence of the phases is not strict and moving back and forth between different phases is always required. The arrows in the process diagram indicate the most important and frequent dependencies between phases. The outer circle in the diagram symbolizes the cyclic nature of data mining itself. A data mining process continues after a solution has been deployed. The lessons learned during the process can trigger new, often more focused business questions and subsequent data mining processes will benefit from the experiences of previous ones.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span &gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span &gt;Process diagram showing the relationship between the different phases of CRISP-DM&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span &gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span  fontWeight="bold"&gt;Business understanding&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span &gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span &gt;This initial phase focuses on understanding the project objectives and requirements from a business perspective, and then converting this knowledge into a data mining problem definition, and a preliminary plan designed to achieve the objectives. A decision model, especially one built using the Decision Model and Notation standard can be used.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span &gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span  fontWeight="bold"&gt;Data understanding&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span &gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span &gt;The data understanding phase starts with an initial data collection and proceeds with activities in order to get familiar with the data, to identify data quality problems, to discover first insights into the data, or to detect interesting subsets to form hypotheses for hidden information.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span &gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span  fontWeight="bold"&gt;Data preparation&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span &gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span &gt;The data preparation phase covers all activities to construct the final dataset (data that will be fed into the modeling tool(s)) from the initial raw data. Data preparation tasks are likely to be performed multiple times, and not in any prescribed order. Tasks include table, record, and attribute selection as well as transformation and cleaning of data for modeling tools.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span &gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span  fontWeight="bold"&gt;Modeling&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span &gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span &gt;In this phase, various modeling techniques are selected and applied, and their parameters are calibrated to optimal values. Typically, there are several techniques for the same data mining problem type. Some techniques have specific requirements on the form of data. Therefore, stepping back to the data preparation phase is often needed.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span &gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span  fontWeight="bold"&gt;Evaluation&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span &gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span &gt;At this stage in the project you have built a model (or models) that appears to have high quality, from a data analysis perspective. Before proceeding to final deployment of the model, it is important to more thoroughly evaluate the model, and review the steps executed to construct the model, to be certain it properly achieves the business objectives. A key objective is to determine if there is some important business issue that has not been sufficiently considered. At the end of this phase, a decision on the use of the data mining results should be reached.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span &gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span  fontWeight="bold"&gt;Deployment&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span &gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span &gt;Creation of the model is generally not the end of the project. Even if the purpose of the model is to increase knowledge of the data, the knowledge gained will need to be organized and presented in a way that is useful to the customer. Depending on the requirements, the deployment phase can be as simple as generating a report or as complex as implementing a repeatable data scoring (e.g. segment allocation) or data mining process. In many cases it will be the customer, not the data analyst, who will carry out the deployment steps. Even if the analyst deploys the model it is important for the customer to understand up front the actions which will need to be carried out in order to actually make use of the created models&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span &gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/TextFlow&gt;</related-content>
	</section>
	<section type="slide" position="29" xmlns="">
		<title>Data Science vs. Big Data</title>
		<content>Data Science vs. Big Data  Data Science vs. Big Data Elham Akhondzadeh, 2020  _ _ _ Data Science vs. Big Data  Data Science vs. Big Data Elham Akhondzadeh, 2020  _ _ _ </content>
		<related-content></related-content>
	</section>
	<section type="slide" position="30" xmlns="">
		<title>Big Data – 6V’s</title>
		<content>Big Data – 6V’s   Variability &amp;amp; Value   Elham Akhondzadeh, 2020 Big Data – 6V’s   Variability &amp;amp; Value   Elham Akhondzadeh, 2020 </content>
		<related-content></related-content>
	</section>
	<section type="slide" position="31" xmlns="">
		<title>IT Engineering Research </title>
		<content>IT Engineering Research&amp;#x0A;  Is transdisciplinary &amp;amp; multidisciplinary  Basic Research (Fundamental or Pure Research for the purpose of contributing to existing body of knowledge) &amp;amp; Applied Research (to solve a current problem) Engages with both theory and practice Research needs to have some practical consequences &amp;amp; Should be undertaken with rigor  Movement between theory and empirical world (VWmodel)  Involves undertaking systematic research  Elham Akhondzadeh, 2020 IT Engineering Research&amp;#x0A;  Is transdisciplinary &amp;amp; multidisciplinary  Basic Research (Fundamental or Pure Research for the purpose of contributing to existing body of knowledge) &amp;amp; Applied Research (to solve a current problem) Engages with both theory and practice Research needs to have some practical consequences &amp;amp; Should be undertaken with rigor  Movement between theory and empirical world (VWmodel)  Involves undertaking systematic research  Elham Akhondzadeh, 2020 </content>
		<related-content></related-content>
	</section>
	<section type="slide" position="32" xmlns="">
		<title>Main References</title>
		<content>Main References  Business Research Methods by Donald Cooper &amp;amp; Pamela Schindler Research Methods for Business Students by Mark Saunders, Philip Lewis &amp;amp; Adrian Thornhill  Elham Akhondzadeh, 2020 Main References  Business Research Methods by Donald Cooper &amp;amp; Pamela Schindler Research Methods for Business Students by Mark Saunders, Philip Lewis &amp;amp; Adrian Thornhill  Elham Akhondzadeh, 2020 </content>
		<related-content></related-content>
	</section>
	<section type="slide" position="33" xmlns="">
		<title></title>
		<content>www.Win2Farsi.com    Q &amp;amp; A www.Win2Farsi.com    Q &amp;amp; A </content>
		<related-content></related-content>
	</section>
</document-metadata>
