<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<document-metadata version="1.0" xmlns="http://breeze.macromedia.com/">
	<document-info>
		<title></title>
		<summary></summary>
		<author/>
		<keywords/>
		<view-link href="/index.htm?slide={{position}}" href-html5="/index.htm?slide={{position}}" href-swf="/viewer.swf?slide={{position}}"/>
	</document-info>
	<section type="slide" position="1" xmlns="">
		<title></title>
		<content>In the name of God Research Methodology Introduction to Research Methodology &amp;amp; the Course  Elham Akhondzadeh Noughabi Assistant Professor, Department of Information Technology Engineering, Faculty of Industrial and Systems Engineering, Tarbiat Modares University  2020 In the name of God Research Methodology Introduction to Research Methodology &amp;amp; the Course  Elham Akhondzadeh Noughabi Assistant Professor, Department of Information Technology Engineering, Faculty of Industrial and Systems Engineering, Tarbiat Modares University  2020 </content>
		<related-content></related-content>
	</section>
	<section type="slide" position="2" xmlns="">
		<title>What is Research? </title>
		<content>What is Research?    Elham Akhondzadeh, 2019 What is Research?    Elham Akhondzadeh, 2019 </content>
		<related-content></related-content>
	</section>
	<section type="slide" position="3" xmlns="">
		<title>What is Research? </title>
		<content>What is Research?  an “organized, systematic, data-based, critical, scientific inquiry or investigation into a specific problem”, undertaken with the “purpose of finding answers or solutions.”  Elham Akhondzadeh, 2019 What is Research?  an “organized, systematic, data-based, critical, scientific inquiry or investigation into a specific problem”, undertaken with the “purpose of finding answers or solutions.”  Elham Akhondzadeh, 2019 </content>
		<related-content></related-content>
	</section>
	<section type="slide" position="4" xmlns="">
		<title>Aims of Research</title>
		<content>Aims of Research  Discover new information or relationships; to expand and to verify existing knowledge  Develop and provide new knowledge; discovery of general principles  Theory building  Investigation of hypothetical propositions about the presumed relations among natural phenomena  To solve problems and for decision making purposes (business &amp;amp; management research) Increase our power to understand &amp;amp; explain, predict, describe &amp;amp; change   Elham Akhondzadeh, 2019 Aims of Research  Discover new information or relationships; to expand and to verify existing knowledge  Develop and provide new knowledge; discovery of general principles  Theory building  Investigation of hypothetical propositions about the presumed relations among natural phenomena  To solve problems and for decision making purposes (business &amp;amp; management research) Increase our power to understand &amp;amp; explain, predict, describe &amp;amp; change   Elham Akhondzadeh, 2019 </content>
		<related-content></related-content>
	</section>
	<section type="slide" position="5" xmlns="">
		<title>The Spirit of Research</title>
		<content>The Spirit of Research  Exploration &amp;amp; Discovery   We require: An appropriate process of discovery &amp;amp; An appropriate communication of research findings   Elham Akhondzadeh, 2019 The Spirit of Research  Exploration &amp;amp; Discovery   We require: An appropriate process of discovery &amp;amp; An appropriate communication of research findings   Elham Akhondzadeh, 2019 </content>
		<related-content></related-content>
	</section>
	<section type="slide" position="6" xmlns="">
		<title>The Nature of Research - Definition</title>
		<content>The Nature of Research - Definition Definition: ‘Something that people undertake in order to find things out in a systematic way, thereby increasing their knowledge’  Saunders et al. (2009)  Characteristics:  Data are collected systematically  Data are interpreted systematically There is a clear purpose to find things out 	  Elham Akhondzadeh, 2019 The Nature of Research - Definition Definition: ‘Something that people undertake in order to find things out in a systematic way, thereby increasing their knowledge’  Saunders et al. (2009)  Characteristics:  Data are collected systematically  Data are interpreted systematically There is a clear purpose to find things out 	  Elham Akhondzadeh, 2019 </content>
		<related-content></related-content>
	</section>
	<section type="slide" position="7" xmlns="">
		<title>Why, What, Where , How &amp; When Questions</title>
		<content>Why, What, Where , How &amp;amp; When Questions What do I want to find out? Why am I doing this research project? Where is the information that I want to find out? How should I answer to the research questions? How will I be assessed? When can I start and when must I finish my work? Elham Akhondzadeh, 2019  Why, What, Where , How &amp;amp; When Questions What do I want to find out? Why am I doing this research project? Where is the information that I want to find out? How should I answer to the research questions? How will I be assessed? When can I start and when must I finish my work? Elham Akhondzadeh, 2019  </content>
		<related-content></related-content>
	</section>
	<section type="slide" position="8" xmlns="">
		<title>How to Do Research: Stages of the Research Process</title>
		<content>How to Do Research: Stages of the Research Process 1. Generating research ideas 2. Reviewing the literature &amp;amp; Focus question 4. Designing the research  5. Collecting data  6. Analyzing data  7. Writing up   3. Writing your research proposal Formulating and clarifying a topic How to Do Research: Stages of the Research Process 1. Generating research ideas 2. Reviewing the literature &amp;amp; Focus question 4. Designing the research  5. Collecting data  6. Analyzing data  7. Writing up   3. Writing your research proposal Formulating and clarifying a topic </content>
		<related-content></related-content>
	</section>
	<section type="slide" position="9" xmlns="">
		<title>Research Process: Factors to consider </title>
		<content>Research Process: Factors to consider  Your personal feelings and beliefs Access to data Time and other resources Validity and reliability of the data &amp;amp; results Ethical issues  Elham Akhondzadeh, 2019 Research Process: Factors to consider  Your personal feelings and beliefs Access to data Time and other resources Validity and reliability of the data &amp;amp; results Ethical issues  Elham Akhondzadeh, 2019 </content>
		<related-content></related-content>
	</section>
	<section type="slide" position="10" xmlns="">
		<title>What is Research Methodology</title>
		<content>What is Research Methodology 'Research methodology' refers to the study of research methods. It does not admit of a plural. The theory of how research should be undertaken  Saunders et al. (2009)  	  A science of studying how research is done scientifically A way to systematically solve the research problem by logically adopting various steps Aims to describe and analyze methods and throw light on their limitations an benefits Researchers should know the relevant method and which are not, know the logic behind the methods we use in the context of our research study and explain why we are using a particular method and why we are not using others  Elham Akhondzadeh, 2019 What is Research Methodology 'Research methodology' refers to the study of research methods. It does not admit of a plural. The theory of how research should be undertaken  Saunders et al. (2009)  	  A science of studying how research is done scientifically A way to systematically solve the research problem by logically adopting various steps Aims to describe and analyze methods and throw light on their limitations an benefits Researchers should know the relevant method and which are not, know the logic behind the methods we use in the context of our research study and explain why we are using a particular method and why we are not using others  Elham Akhondzadeh, 2019 </content>
		<related-content></related-content>
	</section>
	<section type="slide" position="11" xmlns="">
		<title>Why Research Methodology Course</title>
		<content>Why Research Methodology Course Why Do You Need and Choose Research Methodology ?  Elham Akhondzadeh, 2019 Why Research Methodology Course Why Do You Need and Choose Research Methodology ?  Elham Akhondzadeh, 2019 </content>
		<related-content></related-content>
	</section>
	<section type="slide" position="12" xmlns="">
		<title>Why Research Methodology Course</title>
		<content>Why Research Methodology Course This will be your unique opportunity in order to provide a concrete demonstration of your abilities. So: You need an appropriate process of discovery &amp;amp; find a way to communicate the research findings  	  Elham Akhondzadeh, 2019 Why Research Methodology Course This will be your unique opportunity in order to provide a concrete demonstration of your abilities. So: You need an appropriate process of discovery &amp;amp; find a way to communicate the research findings  	  Elham Akhondzadeh, 2019 </content>
		<related-content>&lt;TextFlow xmlns = "http://ns.adobe.com/textLayout/2008" fontFamily = "Verdana" fontSize = "9"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span &gt;دوره تحصيلات تكمبلي يك فرصت استثنايي براي شماست تا نوانمندي خود را بطور ملموس نشان دهيد&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span &gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span &gt;به فرايند ي نيازمنديم كه براي كشف و يافتن مناسب باشد&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span &gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span &gt;بايد راهي را بيابيم تا يافته هاي خود را با ديگران  مكالمه و مبادله  كنيد&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span &gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/TextFlow&gt;</related-content>
	</section>
	<section type="slide" position="13" xmlns="">
		<title>Course description</title>
		<content>Course description The aim of this course is to prepare Master Students in Information Technology Engineering to conduct research across the range of IT disciplines such as information systems, information management, big data, data science, security, Internet of Things, Artificial intelligence and Cloud Computing. In this course, the students will learn the basic skills which are essential to become a successful researcher. The objective of the course is to teach research skills in a systematic fashion, early in a student's graduate program. It explains the nature of research, various research strategies, approaches, methods and techniques that are applicable in the fields of IT. This course introduces the principles of research design, research ethics, research methods and techniques of data collection and analysis appropriate to IT research in academic and industry settings. Skills developed and knowledge acquired from this course will prepare students to conduct and communicate their own research, as well as to be knowledgeable and critical interpreters of others' research. We try to provide the students with hints and solutions which could be helpful while facing routine research challenges.  Elham Akhondzadeh, 2019 Course description The aim of this course is to prepare Master Students in Information Technology Engineering to conduct research across the range of IT disciplines such as information systems, information management, big data, data science, security, Internet of Things, Artificial intelligence and Cloud Computing. In this course, the students will learn the basic skills which are essential to become a successful researcher. The objective of the course is to teach research skills in a systematic fashion, early in a student's graduate program. It explains the nature of research, various research strategies, approaches, methods and techniques that are applicable in the fields of IT. This course introduces the principles of research design, research ethics, research methods and techniques of data collection and analysis appropriate to IT research in academic and industry settings. Skills developed and knowledge acquired from this course will prepare students to conduct and communicate their own research, as well as to be knowledgeable and critical interpreters of others' research. We try to provide the students with hints and solutions which could be helpful while facing routine research challenges.  Elham Akhondzadeh, 2019 </content>
		<related-content></related-content>
	</section>
	<section type="slide" position="14" xmlns="">
		<title>Course objectives</title>
		<content>Course objectives Upon successful completion of this course, students should be able to: know the nature of research and systematic research process design rigorous and ethical Master level research projects and develop project proposals evaluate and select research methods and techniques of data collection and analysis appropriate to particular research designs, projects and disciplines conduct ethical research communicate research findings in written and oral form in research and industry settings critically review research literature, research design and reported findings apply research skills to operate effectively as a member of a research project team  Elham Akhondzadeh, 2019 Course objectives Upon successful completion of this course, students should be able to: know the nature of research and systematic research process design rigorous and ethical Master level research projects and develop project proposals evaluate and select research methods and techniques of data collection and analysis appropriate to particular research designs, projects and disciplines conduct ethical research communicate research findings in written and oral form in research and industry settings critically review research literature, research design and reported findings apply research skills to operate effectively as a member of a research project team  Elham Akhondzadeh, 2019 </content>
		<related-content></related-content>
	</section>
	<section type="slide" position="15" xmlns="">
		<title>Brief contents</title>
		<content>Brief contents  Five Main Parts Fundamentals of Research The Design of Research The Sources and Collection of Data Analysis and Presentation of Data Problem Identification &amp;amp; Formulation Elham Akhondzadeh, 2019 Brief contents  Five Main Parts Fundamentals of Research The Design of Research The Sources and Collection of Data Analysis and Presentation of Data Problem Identification &amp;amp; Formulation Elham Akhondzadeh, 2019 </content>
		<related-content></related-content>
	</section>
	<section type="slide" position="16" xmlns="">
		<title>Course Plan</title>
		<content>Course Plan  Introduction to Research Methodology &amp;amp; the CourseSubject 1   Fundamentals of Research Methodology Subject 2   Generating Research IdeasSubject 3   Critically Reviewing the LiteratureSubject 4   Writing your Research ProposalSubject 5   Research Onion &amp;amp; DesignSubject 6   Ethics in ResearchSubject 7 The Sources and Collection of Data Subject 8 Analyzing Quantitative DataSubject 9 Presenting Insights and FindingsSubject 10 Use of Tools, Methods and Softwares  for Research    Course Plan aligned with Research Process Elham Akhondzadeh, 2019 Course Plan  Introduction to Research Methodology &amp;amp; the CourseSubject 1   Fundamentals of Research Methodology Subject 2   Generating Research IdeasSubject 3   Critically Reviewing the LiteratureSubject 4   Writing your Research ProposalSubject 5   Research Onion &amp;amp; DesignSubject 6   Ethics in ResearchSubject 7 The Sources and Collection of Data Subject 8 Analyzing Quantitative DataSubject 9 Presenting Insights and FindingsSubject 10 Use of Tools, Methods and Softwares  for Research    Course Plan aligned with Research Process Elham Akhondzadeh, 2019 </content>
		<related-content></related-content>
	</section>
	<section type="slide" position="17" xmlns="">
		<title>Reference Textbook(s)</title>
		<content>Reference Textbook(s)  Business Research Methods by Donald Cooper &amp;amp; Pamela Schindler Research Methods for Business Students by Mark Saunders, Philip Lewis &amp;amp; Adrian Thornhill  Research design: Qualitative, quantitative and mixed methods approaches by John W. Creswell   Business Research Methods by Alan Bryman &amp;amp; Emma Bell, Oxford University Press.  Research Project Success: The Essential Guide for Science and Engineering Students Research Methodology by C.R.Kothari  Elham Akhondzadeh, 2019 Reference Textbook(s)  Business Research Methods by Donald Cooper &amp;amp; Pamela Schindler Research Methods for Business Students by Mark Saunders, Philip Lewis &amp;amp; Adrian Thornhill  Research design: Qualitative, quantitative and mixed methods approaches by John W. Creswell   Business Research Methods by Alan Bryman &amp;amp; Emma Bell, Oxford University Press.  Research Project Success: The Essential Guide for Science and Engineering Students Research Methodology by C.R.Kothari  Elham Akhondzadeh, 2019 </content>
		<related-content></related-content>
	</section>
	<section type="slide" position="18" xmlns="">
		<title>Assessment</title>
		<content>Assignments (45%)  Mid-term quiz (15%)  Final exam (35%)   Interaction and Discussion in Class (5%) Elham Akhondzadeh, 2019  Assessment Assignments (45%)  Mid-term quiz (15%)  Final exam (35%)   Interaction and Discussion in Class (5%) Elham Akhondzadeh, 2019  Assessment </content>
		<related-content></related-content>
	</section>
	<section type="slide" position="19" xmlns="">
		<title>Course expectations</title>
		<content>Course expectations What are your expectations for this course? What do you want and/or need to get out of it? What are you anxious about? What are you excited about?   ؟ Elham Akhondzadeh, 2019 Course expectations What are your expectations for this course? What do you want and/or need to get out of it? What are you anxious about? What are you excited about?   ؟ Elham Akhondzadeh, 2019 </content>
		<related-content></related-content>
	</section>
</document-metadata>
